ILGWU. New York Cloak Joint Board records 5780/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: New York Cloak Joint Board Subject Files, 1926-1973
  - ILGWU. (Management) Engineering Dept, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Reports on firms
  - ILGWU. Fair Trade Practices Dept., 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    I.c.w. Matthew Schoenwald (director); reports re import problems.
  - ILGWU. Justice, 1945-1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Articles; incl. Gerechticrkeit
  - ILGWU. Legal Dept., 1950-1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Incl. excerpt from memo, "Wage Controls under the Defense Production Act of 1950" by Morris P Glushien re wagen egotiations during Korean War
  - ILGWU. Master Agreements Dept., 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU. National Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 3], 1967-1973 (Box 14, Folder 3a)
  - ILGWU. National Retirement Fund [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    I.c.w. Arthur Altmeyer & Louis Rolnick, reports.
  - ILGWU. National Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 3], 1967-1973 (Box 14, Folder 4b)
  - ILGWU. Nat'l. Retirement Fund, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    By-laws, rules & regulations (1972).
  - ILGWU. Nat'l. Retirement Fund, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Corres. re merger (1965) of funds of Union affiliates into ILGWU nat'l. fund; rules & regulations (1964).
  - ILGWU. Nat'l. Retirement Fund, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Report of the administrator.
  - ILGWU. Nat'l. Retirement Fund, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Petitions for Pension Plan.
  - ILGWU. Political Dept., 1948-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU. Research Dept. [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    I.c.w. Lazare Teper, reports on imports & wages.
  - ILGWU. Research Dept. [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ILGWU. Retiree Service Dept. [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    I.c.w. David Dubinsky, Zalman Lichtenstein; reports, visiting program, Special Assistance Fund.
  - ILGWU. Retiree Service Dept. [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU. Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1a)
    Reports & corres.
  - ILGWU. Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1b)
  - ILGWU. Supplementary Unemployment Benefits (SUB) Fund, 1960-1968 (Box 16, Folder 2a)
  - ILGWU. SUB Fund, 1962-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2b)
    Administrator's report to board of trustees.
  - ILGWU. SUB Fund, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Board of trustees minutes.
  - ILGWU. Union Label Dept [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Incl. material on "Made in Japan" ad.
  - ILGWU. Union Label Dept [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU. Union Label Dept [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU. Union Label Dept [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU. Union Label Dept., 1962 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    The Keys to Selling the Union to the American Public (1962) and A Study of the Attitudes of American Women Toward Trade Unions in America (May 1962) by Louis Harris & Associates.
  - ILGWU. Unity House, 1948-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Minutes of the GEB Committee; corres.
  - ILGWU. Welfare and Health Benefits Dept., 1955-1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Reports on ILGWU drug plan and Cloak Jt. Bd. dental program; report of the administrator to board of trustees (Dec. 4, 1969); corres.
  - International Solidarity Committee, 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Israel, 1948-1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    I.c.w. congressmen re Israel Aid Act of 1951; Labor Zionist Comm. for Relief & Rehabilitation; speech by Israel Fein-berg, trade union meeting on partition of Palestine, Yankee Stadium (Apr. 14, 1948).
  - Israel, Amun-Israeli Housing Corp, 1950-1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Israel, Histadrut (National Committee for Labor Israel) [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Incl. Averell Harriman ltr.
  - Israel, Histadrut (National Committee for Labor Israel) [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Israel, Manhattan Center Mass Rally, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    March 1, 1948. Jt. Bd. meeting on partition of Palestine.
  - Italian-American Labor Council, 1945-1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Daily Forward, NYC, Boston, Los Angeles, 1941-1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1958-1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Corres., draft resolutions, statements.
  - J.L.C. [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1966 (Box 19, Folder 1a)
    Incl. "The Crisis of the Free World" (speech, 1956) by I. Nagler; "German Rearmament? The French View" (article, 1950) by Daniel Mayer.
  - J.L.C. [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1966 (Box 19, Folder 1b)
  - J.L.C., 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 1c)
    Corres. re adoption of orphans; trip to Europe by I. Feinberg (1949).
  - Jewish Sanatorium Hospital for Chronic Diseases, Brooklyn, N.Y., 1947-1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Joint Boards, Los Angeles Cloak [folder 1 of 2], 1939-1967 (Box 19, Folder 3a)
    I.c.w. Isidor Stenzor, Louis Pine & I. Lutsky; L.A. negotiations (1964, 1967).
  - Joint Boards, Los Angeles Cloak [folder 2 of 2], 1939-1967 (Box 19, Folder 3b)
  - Jt. Bd., Los Angeles Dress, 1942-1948 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    I.c.w. Fannie Borax & George Wishnak.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Installation of officers, Incl. Corres., photographs.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Installation of officers; incl. report of general manager, lists of executive board members, speeches, corres.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Installation of officers; incl. speeches.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Installation of officers; incl. speeches and congratulatory messages when H.Mendelsund became general manager of Jt. Bd. (Sept. 1959) and vice-president (Jan. 1960), of Union.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Installation of officers; incl. speeches and corres.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1940-1953 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Installation of officers, incl. I. Nagler as general manager (1952).
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak [folder 1 of 4], 1949-1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Research Dept.; reports, surveys of annual earnings by Roy Helfgott, press releases and corres.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak [folder 2 of 4], 1949-1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak [folder 3 of 4], 1949-1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak [folder 4 of 4], 1949-1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak, 1939-1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Statistical data, financial statements & reports on membership, lists of jobbers & contractors (1939).
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak and Dress, 1926-1928 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Incl. Union releases.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Cloak. n.d. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Historical & general information on Jt. Bd.
  - Jt. Bd., N.Y. Dress, 1943-1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Statements & corres., pamphlets.
  - Jt. Bd., South Jersey-Philadelphia, 1940-1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. Barnett Karp, Morris Dobren & Harry Benn.
  - Jt. Bd., Miscellaneous, 1948-1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Jurisdictional Disputes, Inter-Union, 1947-1958 (Box 21, Folder 3a)
    I.c.w. Jacob Potofsky re Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.
  - Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1948-1959 (Box 21, Folder 3b)
    Locals 23, 25, 66, 91 & 105; incl. GEB Comm. reports.
  - K, 1950-1965 (Box 21, Folder 4a)
  - L, 1940-1966 (Box 21, Folder 4b)
    I.c.w. Fiorello La Guardia, Samuel Lefkovitz, Herbert H. Lehman; Life of a Cloakmaker controversy (Meyer Kushner-Harry Lang); memo of meeting re visit of contractors to Unity House with I. Feinberg, R. Zuckerman & Hyman Libow present (1940).
  - Labor Aid Project, 1947-1948 (Box 21, Folder 4c)
    Executive board minutes; fund raising corres.
  - Labor Day Greetings, 1950-1972 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Articles for newspapers
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1943-1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Fund raising; i.c.w. Students for a Democratic Society.
  - Legal Feasibility of Importing into United States Polish Garment Workers, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Memo by James Lipsig to David Dubinsky.
  - Legislation, 1940-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    I.c.w. legislators in Albany & Washington; ltrs. from Jacob Javits, Herbert Lehman & Nelson Rockefeller; statement on Hatch-Ashberry Bill (1958).
  - Liberal Party, 1949-1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Local 9, NYC, 1953-1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    I.c.w. Harry Fisher & Louis Hyman; printed material.
  - Local 9, NYC, 1953-1968 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Annual reports (1967 & 1963); Examination Committee, 1953; election leaflets, 1950-68.
  - Local 10, NYC, 1942-1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. Abe Dolgen & Moe Falikman.
  - Local 10, NYC. n.d. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Election leaflets.
  - Local 20, NYC, 1949-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    I.c.w. Sam Fine & Joe Kessler.
  - Local 23-25, NYC, 1963-1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    I.c.w. Shelley Appleton.
  - Local 23, NYC [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    I.c.w. Shelley Appleton & Louis Reiss; manager's reports to membership meetings (1945-53); printed matter.
  - Local 23, NYC [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Local 30, NYC, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Local 32, NYC, 1940-1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    I.c.w. Abraham Snyder, & Julius Ramirez.
  - Local 35, NYC, 1945-1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    I.c.w. Joseph Breslaw & Morris Kovler; organizing drive (1949); plan for guaranteed terra of employment (1950); Local 35 News (Apr. 1958 & April 1960); printed material.
  - Local 48, NYC [folder 1 of 2], 1943-1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    I.c.w. Edward Molisani & E. Howard Molisani; rules & regulations of Local (n.d.); printed material.
  - Local 48, NYC [folder 2 of 2], 1943-1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Local 64, NYC, 1948-1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Incl. Corres. re negotiations.
  - Local 82, NYC, 1943-1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    I.c.w. Charles Bernstein, Joshua Fogel, & Violet Watson; negotiations; printed material.
  - Local 99, NYC, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Constitution & by-laws of Health & Welfare Fund of Local (1973); corres
  - Local 102, NYC, 1941-1955 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    I.c.w. Sain Berger.
  - Local 105, NYC, 1948-1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Incl. Corres. re jurisdictional questions bet. Locals 23 & 105; Leadership Conference (1963); corres. w. Martin Cohen.
  - Local 117, NYC [folder 1 of 2], 1936-1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    I.c.w. Nat Windman & Benjamin Kaplan; Finance Comm. report; printed material.
  - Local 117, NYC [folder 2 of 2], 1936-1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Local 155, NYC, 1947-1949 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    I.c.w. Louis Nelson, printed material, press releases.
  - Locals, Miscellaneous, 1942-1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Jack Spitzer's statement on enforced resignation as mgr- secy, Local 60 (1959); copy of ltr. sent by Charles S. Zimmerman on conditions in N.Y. Central Trades & Labor Council (1950).
  - Local Managers' (N.Y. Cloak) Conferences, 1945-1955 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - London, Meyer, Memorial Committee, 1951-1955 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Speeches at memorial (1951) on 25th anniversary of death.
  - London, Meyer, Public School no.2, 1958-1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Incl. speeches at dedication, photographs.
  - M, 1941-1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Incl. copy of Marianne Moore ltr. & memo by H.M. to I.N. re John Marsh (n.d.).
  - Maltese, Antonio, Case, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Appeal Committee Case #901, accusation & transcript of Grievance Comm. meeting (May 6, 1952), decision of Appeal Comm.
  - Mannish Suit and Overlapping Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd., 1939-1955 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Corres. with Benjamin Moser & Charles Oronsky; incl. reports.
  - Markewich and Null, 1940-1945 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Corres. re People (Vito Trimarco) vs Giuseppe Fristachi and assaults on Hyman Libow and Samuel Zeldin.
  - Mendelsund, Henoch, 1951-1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Awards, security information data (1968); ltr. of thanks from Sol C. Chaikin (May 28, 1971
  - Mendelsund, Henoch, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Speeches and reports.
  - Mendelsund, Henoch. Photographs. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Merchants-American Department, Cloak Joint Board [folder 1 of 3], 1942-1961 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    I.c.w. John Denaro, Hyman Libow, Harry Fein, Harry Slutzky, M. Bagno; reports.
  - Merchants-American Department, Cloak Joint Board [folder 2 of 3], 1942-1961 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Merchants-American Department, Cloak Joint Board [folder 3 of 3], 1942-1961 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Merchant Ladies Garment Association, Inc., 1943-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. Joseph Dubow.
  - Miscellaneous, 1948-1951 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Modecraft Coat Co., 1963-1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    I.c.w. Harry Benn, William Ross; workers' complaints; lists of workers.
  - Modern Review, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Fund raising ltrs.
  - N, 1957-1972 (Box 25, Folder 5a)
  - Nagler, Isidore, 1952-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5b)
    Personal corres., incl. ltr. re Communism and academic freedom.
  - Nagler, Isidore [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1958 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Speeches & reports.
  - Nagler, Isidore [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1958 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Nagler, Isidore, 1935-1938 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Speeches.
  - Nagler, Isidore, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Condolences on death, speeches at funeral, newspaper clippings & press releases.
  - Nagler, Isidore. Photographs. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Nagler Hall (Isidore), 1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Corres. re cornerstone & dedication, ceremonies, photos.
  - Nagler Youth Center, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Corres. & photos.
  - National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry [folder 1 of 3], 1948-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    (National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board I.c.w. Joseph Batchker, Joseph Dubow, Wilbur Daniels, Samuel Baron, Joseph Rubin; also Incl. Corres. re import questions.
  - National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry [folder 2 of 3], 1948-1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry [folder 3 of 3], 1948-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Corres. re labor relations course at Fashion Institute of Technology.
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Minutes, reports to board of directors, statements by D.D. (n.d.), "A Program for the Recovery Board" (1960), "Report of Cessation of Operations" (1972) & resolutions re dissolution of Board (1973).
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Statement by Wilbur Daniels before Federal Trade Commission re Textile Fiber Products Identification Act (1964); statement on imports (1967).
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Trial Examiner's Recommended Decision to Federal Trade Commission in the matter of Nat'l. Assoc. of Blouse Mfrs. Inc., Charles Kreindler, et al.; Webster Ballinger (trial examiner).
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry, Conventions, 1962-1964 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Corres., reports, photographs.
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry, Conventions [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 1a)
    Corres., resolutions, photographs.
  - Nat'l. Bd. of the Coat and Suit Industry, Conventions [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 1b)
  - National Educational Committee for a New Party, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Corres. & minutes.
  - Nat'l. Educational Committee for a New Party, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Newsletter & printed material
  - National Farm Labor Union, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Fundraising requests
  - National Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1943-1961 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Organizing drive (1952), negotiations of contracts with Union, statements by Union (1953 & 1958), press releases, corres
  - Negotiations, 1968-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Negotiations [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7a)
  - Negotiations [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7b)
  - Negotiations [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7c)
  - Negotiations [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1a)
  - Negotiations [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1b)
  - Negotiations, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Negotiations, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Negotiations, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Negotiations, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Negotiations [folder 1 of 2], 1951 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Negotiations [folder 2 of 2], 1951 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Negotiations, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Negotiations, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Negotiations, 1940-1943 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - New York Coat and Suit Association, Inc., 1961-1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. Joseph Dubow, releases, statements.
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1955-1962 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Corres., memorandum of joint meeting of State Federation of Labor & State CIO Council Merger Comm. (1957).
  - Newspapers, 1962-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Corres., articles.
  - Non-assessables, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Corres. & reports re items exempt from employer's contributions to benefit funds.
  - Northeast Department, 1951-1955 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    I.c.w. Sol C. Chaikin, David Gingold, Sol Greene, Jack Halpern
  - O, 1961-1966 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Office Employees Int'l. Union, Local 153, 1939-1953 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Corres., agreements w. Union.
  - Organization Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd., 1948-1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    I.c.w. Harry Lopatin, memos, leaflets.
  - Organization Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd., 1948-1960 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    I.c.w. Mark Horowitz, memos, leaflets.
  - Organization Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1966 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    (Organization & Patrol Dept.) Reports from Ph. Herman, Max Horowitz, Mayer Finkel.
  - Organization Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1966 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Organization Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1947 (Box 30, Folder 1a)
    (Organization & Patrol Dept.) Reports by Ph. Herman.
  - Organization Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 2], 1941-1947 (Box 30, Folder 1b)
  - Organizational Drive, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 2a)
    Corres., reports, statements, plans for organizing workers, headed by Isidore Nagler.
  - Organizational Drive, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 2b)
    Press clippings.
  - Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training in Industry and Agriculture (ORT), 1948-1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Overlapping Campaign [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1949 (Box 30, Folder 4a)
    Corres., reports, leaflets re organizing workers in Bond factories in Rochester, N.Y.; I.c.w. Ralph A. Roberts.
  - Overlapping Campaign [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1949 (Box 30, Folder 4b)
  - Overlapping Department, ILGWU [folder 1 of 2], 1936-1949 (Box 30, Folder 5a)
    Reports by B. Moser & George Wishnak; jurisdictional disputes intra-Union & w. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; D.D. ltr. to Sidney Hillman; "Encroachment of Men's Clothing Establishment on the Women's Coat and Suit Industry" by Israel Feinberg (1943?).
  - Overlapping Department, ILGWU [folder 2 of 2], 1936-1949 (Box 30, Folder 5b)
  - Overlapping Dept., ILGWU, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Organizational drive headed by Joseph Breslaw; reports; jurisdictional dispute w. ACWA.
  - P, 1941-1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Peck and Peck, 1952-1954 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Corres. re organization of workers producing garments for sale by Peck & Peck.
  - Personnel, 1965-1973 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Job applications, Murray Sontag murder.
  - Piece-Rate Settlements, 1934-1967 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Grading systems & calculations; "Digest of Labor Bureau Report" by N.I. Stone (1935); minutes of staff meeting (1962).
  - Polish-American Branch, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1938-1961 (Box 31, Folder 2a)
    Memo concerning termination of Branch, mailing lists, Elections & Objection Comm. minutes (1959, 1962).
  - Political Activities, 1951-1965 (Box 31, Folder 2b)
    Ltrs. re elections, (non -Union).
  - Price Adjustment Department, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1959 (Box 31, Folder 3a)
    I.c.w. I. Stenzor, I. Block; reports.
  - Price Adjustment Department, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 2], 1941-1959 (Box 31, Folder 3b)
  - Reefer Department, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 3], 1941-1969 (Box 31, Folder 5a)
    (Children's Coat Dept. from 1962) Managers' reports.
  - Reefer Department, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 3], 1941-1969 (Box 31, Folder 5b)
  - Reefer Department, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 3 of 3], 1941-1969 (Box 31, Folder 5c)
  - Regions and Districts, 1946-1950 (Box 31, Folder 6a)
    I.c.w. Sol Chaikin, Meyer Perlstein, & John Martin; Frederick Siems ltr. (1969).
  - Registration Committee, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1948-1957 (Box 31, Folder 6b)
    Minutes; incl. Designation Comm. minutes.
  - Reports, Board of Directors [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1958 (Box 32, Folder 1a)
    Minutes.
  - Reports, Board of Directors [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1958 (Box 32, Folder 1b)
  - Reports, Board of Directors [folder 1 of 2], 1938-1947 (Box 32, Folder 2a)
  - Reports, Board of Directors [folder 2 of 2], 1938-1947 (Box 32, Folder 2b)
  - Reports (General Manager) to Union Convention, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Reports (General Manager) to Cloak Jt. Bd., 1957-1960 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Reports (General Manager) to Cloak Jt. Bd., 1954-1956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Reports (General Manager) to Cloak Jt. Bd., 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Reports (General Manager) to Cloak Jt. Bd., 1944-1950 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Reports (General Manager) to Cloak Jt. Bd., 1938-1943 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Also undated reports.
  - Resolutions. n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Presented to Union convention by Cloak Jt. Bd. on legislative matters.
  - Retirement, 1950-1970 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Studies re attitudes of workers towards retirement; i.c.w. Merlyn Pitzele; also statistical data, "Report of Union Committee on the Survey of the Attitudes of Cloakmakers Toward Retirement" (Nov. 16, 1951) by Roy Helfgott, Henoch Mendelsund & Joseph Shane and "Personnel Policy and Older Workers" by Lazare Teper (1954).
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1959-1965 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    I.c.w. Arthur, David Dubinsky; age analyses for actuarial purposes; statements; reports on Fund's financial status; special requests to retire; press releases.
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1953-1955 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1949-1952 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    I.c.w. Arthur Altmeyer; resignation of Herbert Zame; agreement with Local 23076, Office Employees (n.d.).
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1943-1945 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. Arthur Altmeyer, Lazare Teper; "Retirement Fund Provision in Collective Agreement Between Associations and Cloak Joint Board" (June 1, 1943).
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, Investment Committee, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    "Advisory Opinion Submitted to the Investment Committee of the Retirement Board of the Coat and Suit Industry of N.Y." and "Reply" by Ira Koenig, attorney for Mrs. Raymond Ingersoll.
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1944-1962 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Rules and regulations.
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, Special Investigating Committee, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Transcript of meeting (May 8, 1952).
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, Special Investigating Committee, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Transcript of meeting (Aug. 13, 1952).
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, Special Investigating Committee, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Report.
  - Retirement Fund, Skirt and Sportswear Industry, 1954-1961 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, Dwight Edwards [folder 1 of 2], 1947 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Collective Bargaining and Market Control in the N.Y. Coat and Suit Industry (manuscript).